kallout.com 2009-05-08

# KallOut - Search Outside the Box

  1. Information Collection & Use
  2. Information Sharing and Disclosure
  3. Legal Disclaimer
  4. Security
  5. Contact Us

## 1\. Information Collection & Use

We are committed to protecting online user privacy. In order to ensure your privacy, information we collect is used only in the manner and for the purposes described below. 

### 1.1 Registration

KallOut, Inc. ("KallOut") does not currently require registration to use the KallOut selection-based search application. Therefore it does not collect personally identifiable information when you use the KallOut selection-based search application. If, in the future, KallOut does support end-user registration (e.g., via e-mail and password) then KallOut will be able to link your use of the KallOut application with your e-mail address (which is personally identifiable information). KallOut is the sole owner of any non-personally identifiable information collected by the KallOut selection-based search application (e.g., user metrics for analyzing application usage, user actions related to advertising clicks, system configuration information useful for debugging and enhancing KallOut).

### 1.2 Children's Privacy Policy

KallOut is not directed towards children 13 years of age or under and we do not knowingly collect any information from children 13 years of age or under through our application. However, because the KallOut application is installed at the desktop level of the operating system, it may inadvertently collect information from children 13 years of age or under who are using the same computer as someone who installed the application on the system.

### 1.3 Uses of Information

KallOut uses information for the following general purposes: to suggest BestGuess™ menu items in the KallOut Menu, to obtain relevant advertising content, to return search results in KallOut information palettes, to customize the search results and sponsored results over selected applications (initially including: Outlook, Word, Excel, PowerPoint, IE6, IE7 and Firefox), improve our services, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

We do not maintain any history of your search terms that is connected with your specific non-personally identifiable user cookie. Nor do we retain any record of text selections that are sent to our servers to determine if there are BestGuess menu items related to any text that you might select inside one of the applications that KallOut enhances.

### 1.4 Profile

We store information that we collect through client-side cookies and server-side log files to create a "profile" of your settings and preferences. At the point in time we add user registration, we will tie your personally identifiable information to information in the profile in order to provide tailored search results and sponsored results for you. We share your profile with other third parties in aggregate form only. 

## 2\. Information Sharing and Disclosure

### 2.1 Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners. This information does not identify individual users. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.

### 2.2 Personally identifiable information:

We DO NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties.

## 3\. Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site

### 3.1 Log Files

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), operating system, date/time stamp, and click-stream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the application and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

### 3.2 Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but the ability for our service to provide accurate personalization for you will be limited. 

### 3.3 Third Party Search Engines

When you execute a query on selected search engines by requesting a KallOut information palette be displayed, the KallOut selection-based search application may make, on your behalf on either your client machine or on our servers, additional network connections to the search engine and execute additional queries. The additional search engine queries may affect the search engine's own personalization algorithms.

### 3.4 Third Party Advertisers

The ads that we deliver to users may be provided by our advertising partners. We share Web site usage information about users with reputable third parties for the purpose of targeting our advertisements on this site. The information that our advertising partners collect is not personally identifiable.

## 4\. Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us atFeedback@KallOut.com.

### 4.1 Business Transitions

In the event KallOut goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred.

### 4.2 Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by means of a notice on our home page.

## 5\. Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [Feedback@kallout.com](mailto:Feedback@kallout.com).
